[{"question": " hey! so what do you think?", "answer": " new haircut?  necklace?  dress?  boots?  boots!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna miss being able to afford food.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, they just, they just look so good! and the saleswoman was looking at me like, &quot;oh, these are way too expensive for you.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh my god!  oh monica! those boots are amazing!", "answer": " they&#146;re mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah well, too bad we&#146;re gonna have to return them.", "answer": " return them?! shh! they&#146;re gonna hear you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " honey, i&#146;m not returning them. okay? i mean i-i know they cost a lot, but i&#146;m going to wear them all the time. you&#146;ll see. besides, i love the compliments. i mean, have you ever had something so beautiful everyone wanted it?", "answer": " i have you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " that&#146;s right, i love you! and-and i&#146;m gonna play with you all the time.", "answer": " how can you let him talk to your crotch like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  he&#146;s talking to the baby.", "answer": " ohh! okay! okay, cause when-when he said, &quot;i can&#146;t wait to hear your first words,&quot; i thought, &quot;there&#146;s a trick.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " okay. well, i gotta go you guys. i&#146;ll see you later.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh hey rach, listen&#151;hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " umm, can you do me a favor? i was talkin&#146; to my sister and she knows you work at ralph lauren&#133;", "answer": " no, forget it! no way! i am not sending anymore ralph lauren clothes to prison. it is a waste.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " no-no-no-no-no-no, not her, not her. my youngest sister, dina, she&#146;s really interested in fashion, and she wants to talk to someone successful, y&#146;know, to give her some advice.", "answer": " i guess i can talk to one of my supervisors&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh no-no-no-no, she wants to talk to you!", "answer": " really?! oh my god! i&#146;m successful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " okay, so will you meet with her?", "answer": " yes! i&#146;d love to! have her come by the office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " great! thanks! you&#146;re gonna love her so much. and&#151;oh, she&#146;s the smartest of all the tribbiani children. hey, y&#146;know the s.a.t&#146;s?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey ross! doesn&#146;t ben go to the smithfield day school?", "answer": " yeah. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " sting has a son that goes there too!", "answer": " yeah i know; he&#146;s in ben&#146;s class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " you knew this and you never said anything?! with all the stupid dinosaur stuff you tell us?!", "answer": " fine! no more dinosaur stuff! can i talk about fossils?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " sting&#146;s son, seven years old and there&#146;s a picture.", "answer": " what are you reading? the kidnappers guide to manhattan private schools?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s new york magazine. it&#146;s an article about the best schools in the city. so how well do you know sting?", "answer": " uh, i actually haven&#146;t even met him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " uh-huh, yeah that&#146;s too bad. i really want to go to his concert friday night, but it&#146;s totally sold out. i know! why don&#146;t you meet him and get tickets?! if you get two i&#146;ll take you.", "answer": " well actually, i&#146;m picking ben up tomorrow, maybe he&#146;ll be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hey-hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " hi monica!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " hi boots.", "answer": " see chandler? i&#146;m getting a lot of use out of them already! they&#146;re very practical. see, you can wear them with dresses, with skirts, with pants&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " wow! they&#146;re beautiful!", "answer": " ahh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  they hurt so much!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " the guy who made these hates feet and wants to see them die!", "answer": " well-well you can give them to me! i haven&#146;t felt my feet in years!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " i can&#146;t! i spent so much money on them and i told chandler that i&#146;d wear them all the time, i just can&#146;t give them away!", "answer": " well then get your money back and return them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i can&#146;t do that either! the soles&#146; are already a little scuffed up and the insides are filled with my blood.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey i uh just picked up ben from school&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t think you did a very thorough job!", "answer": " i dropped him off at carol&#146;s.  anyway, it turns out that i&#146;m not going to be able to get those tickets though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh no! why not?", "answer": " well it turns out that ben and sting&#146;s son do not get along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " how come?!", "answer": " apparently, sting&#146;s son made fun of the fact that ben&#146;s moms are lesbinims.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " wait! but ross if they don&#146;t get along then you should smooth things over. make them be friends.", "answer": " phoebe, you can&#146;t force kids to be friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " sure you can! give them some blocks, put them in a playpen!", "answer": " playpen?! ben&#146;s seven!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " your kid is seven?!   he&#146;s really small.  please! please get the tickets!", "answer": " look i&#146;m sorry pheebs, i can&#146;t do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yes you can! sting says so himself!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  rosssss can!", "answer": " look phoebe, i&#146;m sorry it&#146;s just&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  rossss can!", "answer": " phoebe, i&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  here she is! future fashion superstar!", "answer": " oh joey, i&#146;m hardly a&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " my little sister dina!", "answer": " right! hi dina!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " nice to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " thanks so much for meetin&#146; with me. joey&#146;s told me so much about you!", "answer": " this is so exciting for her. well, i&#146;ll let you two fash&#133;ists get down to business.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " okay. all right dina, well let&#146;s talk about the different areas of fashion that you could get involved in. let&#146;s see, there&#146;s design, but you may need a whole other degree for that. uh, there&#146;s-there&#146;s sales, which is great because you get to travel&#133;", "answer": " i&#133;i don&#146;t care about fashion! i&#146;m pregnant! and i know you are too, so you gotta help me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  ahhhhhhhh!", "answer": "  what&#146;s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " honey, we don&#146;t really have to go to this thing tonight do we?", "answer": " now sweetie, i know you don&#146;t like my office parties, but you can wear your new boots. see? every cloud has a&#133;supple leather lining.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i-i don&#146;t-i don&#146;t think that i&#146;m gonna wear the boots tonight.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " well y&#146;know, i&#146;m just-i&#146;m just worried that bosses will see them and think they pay you too much money. or! or your assistant will see them and-and want a raise!", "answer": " do you think i work at some kind of boot pricing company?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " anyway, i picked up this outfit that i want to wear and the, and the boots don&#146;t really go with it.", "answer": " you said that you paid all that money because those boots go with skirts, dresses, and pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " fine! if you want me to wear the boots, i&#146;ll wear the boots. in fact, i&#146;ll go into my room right now and y&#146;know try the outfit on.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i-i can&#146;t go in there. i can&#146;t tell him!", "answer": " honey, it&#146;s going to be okay. he&#146;s been incredibly supportive of me, and if he gets a little upset; that&#146;s what the meatball sub is for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hey! it&#146;s my fashion girls!  what&#146;s wrong?", "answer": " honey, why don&#146;t you sit down? dina has something that she wants to tell you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  oh. what&#146;s, what&#146;s going on? is it mom? is she sick? is it dad&#146;s heart? is that a sandwich?", "answer": " joe, mom and dad are fine&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " is that a sandwich?!", "answer": " joey&#133;there&#146;s something that you&#133;should know. dina?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i&#146;m pregnant.", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " well obviously this is a mistake! you can&#146;t be pregnant! because you have to have sex to get pregnant!", "answer": " joe, i tried to wait until i was 25 like you did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what?! dina&#133;", "answer": "  bub!!!   i can&#146;t believe this! you&#146;re the good one! you went to college! both years! who did this to you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " bobby corso, but he&#146;s a real nice guy. i like him a lot. he&#146;s real funny.", "answer": " you got pregnant for funny?! dina&#133;if he&#146;s funny&#133;laugh! all right, i&#146;ll be back in a little while! you stay here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " why? where are you going?", "answer": " i can&#146;t look at you right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " wow.", "answer": " i know.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh, there you are ben!", "answer": " aunt phoebe, what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, i heard you&#146;re having a problem with one of the boys in your class. and so i thought i would just come down here and sit you both down, have a little talk and make it all okay. now umm, the boy&#146;s name is sting&#146;s son.", "answer": " jack? i hate him! he&#146;s a jerk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " now ben, sometimes people may seem like jerks on the outside, but they have famous fathers.", "answer": " i have to go. my friend doug is waiting for me over there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " excuse me. can, can i help you with something?", "answer": " yes! yes you can, i&#146;m looking for jack&#146;s parents.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " are you with one of the students?", "answer": " uh-huh, i&#146;m with ben.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " are you one of ben&#146;s mothers?", "answer": " i am one of ben&#146;s mothers. i&#146;m a lesbian. it was, it was difficult coming out to my parents.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well hi, i&#146;m jenny boone. i&#146;m the new teacher here.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i&#146;ve only met your partner carol.", "answer": " ah! okay so that would make me susan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " right. are you looking for jack&#146;s parents to discuss the problems he&#146;s having with ben?  yeah. because i really do think the parents should sit down and have a conversation.", "answer": " yeah! let&#146;s do that!! that-that sounds good. we should sit down and talk, just me, my lover carol, and the stings. umm, how-how will i get in touch with them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh, their number is on the contact sheet.", "answer": " uh-huh. uh-huh. umm, could-could i get a copy of that? &#145;cause carol threw it out, she lost ours. she&#146;s such a scatterbrain, but man what a hot piece of ass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " y&#146;know, that party wasn&#146;t bad.", "answer": " yeah! i didn&#146;t know there would be dancing. that was a fun surprise!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " i don&#146;t see any uh, cabs. maybe we should just walk?", "answer": " oh no, we can&#146;t walk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what honey, it&#146;s like fifteen blocks to the subway. let&#146;s", "answer": " hey! do you think that we can get to the subway right there if we climb down through the manhole cover?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " i can&#146;t walk. okay? okay? these boots were a huge mistake!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " okay you were right! all right, i never should have bought them! they&#146;re killing me! one toe at a time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " so i was right. this is what it feels like to be right.  it&#146;s oddly unsettling.", "answer": " how are we gonna get home? maybe a piggy-back ride?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hop on.", "answer": " okay. wait, just give me a second, i need to just get my boots off first.  ah&#133;ooh&#133;oohh&#133;ohh&#133;oh god&#133;ohh&#133;oh&#133;ohh&#133;ohhhh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " do you ever worry that you&#146;ll be walking and your baby will just like slip out?", "answer": " what college was that dina?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh my god! bobby!", "answer": " hi dina. good to see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " joey, what are you doing?", "answer": " just what needs to be done! dearly beloved, we are gathered here to join this man and this woman&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh joey this is crazy!", "answer": " don&#146;t interrupt me when i&#146;m talkin&#146; to god! now where were we? oh right, okay. do you dina, take this man&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " oh you&#146;ll take &#145;em!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no i won&#146;t!", "answer": " hey! you don&#146;t get a say in this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " yes i do!", "answer": " ahhh! i heard &quot;i do&quot;, we&#146;re halfway there! okay!  you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " all right joey! that is enough!  listen, as beautiful and moving as this ceremony is, it&#146;s not legal. okay? they-they don&#146;t have a marriage license, they don&#146;t have any witnesses, and the groom only has on one shoe!", "answer": " yeah, he took the other one off and hit me with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " well what am i supposed to do?", "answer": " you&#146;re supposed to realize that they are adults! and that they can make their own decisions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " no they can&#146;t! they were stupid enough to get knocked up!", "answer": " heyyyyy! contraceptives are not always effective!  right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah&#133;we kinda didn&#146;t use any&#133;", "answer": " oh, come on kids! a little help here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " i&#146;m trudie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " you must be ben&#146;s mum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " why else would i be here?", "answer": " do sit down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i gather jack and ben haven&#146;t been getting along lately.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i&#146;m told there are two sides to this story, but all i&#146;ve heard is that ben&#146;s a bit of a poo-poo head.", "answer": " umm, i&#146;m sorry. won&#146;t-won&#146;t jack&#146;s father be joining", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh i&#146;m sorry, jack&#146;s father is not available.", "answer": " uh-hmm. okay. well then, could we reschedule? for say, friday night perhaps at 8 o&#146;clock?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh no, i know that wouldn&#146;t work. my husband&#146;s in concert.", "answer": " concert. yeah. that does put us in&#133;quite a pickle. because you see i&#146;m very busy before and after the concert, and he&#146;s obviously busy during.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " so, i guess you and i should talk about jack and ben right now.", "answer": " unless! unless umm, okay i-i would be willing to go to the concert, umm, all the while thinking about the children of course.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " are you here for tickets?", "answer": " oh, thank you. four would be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " i&#146;m not giving concert tickets to someone who&#146;d use their son like this!", "answer": " oh good! then you&#146;re in luck! ben&#146;s not my son!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  look, i&#146;ve just pressed a button, triggering a silent alarm. any minute now, the police will be here!", "answer": " the police? here? a reunion?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " okay, ten blocks down. five to go.", "answer": "  oh wait! stop! stop! stop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh i&#146;m sorry! do you need a break?", "answer": " my boots in tan! hey! can you get a little closer so i can see the price?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i can see it from right here. it&#146;ll cost you one husband.", "answer": " okay, i&#146;m sorry. i think i can walk the rest of the way now. just-just give me my boots.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t have your boots.", "answer": " well i don&#146;t have them either. where are they?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " well, why don&#146;t you check in one of my saddlebags while i chew on a bale of hay!", "answer": " okay.  god well, we gotta go back and get them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " honey, are you seriously ever gonna wear the boots again?", "answer": " okay, i&#146;m never gonna wear them again. i just didn&#146;t get a chance to say goodbye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? you can say goodbye to the tan ones.", "answer": " okay.  all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " joey, just because they&#146;re not getting married doesn&#146;t mean this is going to be a disaster. maybe they have a plan!", "answer": " oh? oh! okay! okay! let&#146;s hear their plan! now, what&#146;s the future look like for dina and bobby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " well&#133;i really have high hopes for my band.", "answer": "  you were right. he is funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hey, now wait a minute! i get when you told people at first that you wanted to be an actor they laughed at you! now come on bobby, why don&#146;t you tell us a little bit about your band?", "answer": " well it&#146;s just me and my pal rooster, the band&#146;s name is numb nuts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " dina, if you&#146;re having a baby you should be married! even if it is to bobby!  dude, that&#146;s not a compliment!", "answer": " no joey! i knew you wouldn&#146;t be supportive!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " so whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! what are you gonna do? you&#146;re gonna have the baby and-and raise it by yourself&#133;without a husband?! you can&#146;t be a single mother alone! you&#146;re gonna ruin your life!", "answer": " oh excuse me! am i ruining my life?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no! no! no! it&#146;s different for you. you&#146;re so strong and together. you&#146;re not some dumb kid who doesn&#146;t know what she&#146;s doing.", "answer": " excuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " one pregnant woman at a time, please! i just want you to be okay.", "answer": " so forcing her to marry bobby is gonna make that happen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " maybe!  well! well&#133;so-so uh, what kind of music does numb nuts&#151;oh forget it! i can&#146;t!", "answer": " joey, i am scared to death about this. but i really think i can do it, i&#146;m just gonna need some help. and bobby&#146;s gonna be here the whole time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " look, rachel&#146;s told me how much easier you&#146;ve made all this on her. why can&#146;t you do that for me?", "answer": " because! &#145;cause&#133; &#145;cause you&#146;re my baby sister!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " and you&#146;re my big brother! i mean, you&#146;re my favorite guy in the whole world. i&#146;m not even scared to tell mom and dad. i was scared of telling you.", "answer": " well i&#146;d be scared of them, but all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " joey, i can&#146;t stand the thought of having this baby with you mad at me. i want him to have his uncle. is my baby gonna have his uncle joey?", "answer": " of course he&#146;s gonna have his uncle joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " we&#146;re gonna be all right. i mean, even if we&#146;re not married this baby is gonna be so loved. not just by us.", "answer": " that&#146;s right! by his uncle too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " and by you.", "answer": " okay bobby, why don&#146;t we just come over here and let them have a little moment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " oh my god! i do love you! how did you do it?!", "answer": " well&#133;let&#146;s just say&#133;  rosss caaaaan!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " oo, where are the seats?", "answer": " uh, middle balcony.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " okay, now would you say that that&#146;s more than 50 yards away from sting, his wife, or a member of his family?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}]